Week three. Day one. Fighting for animals. A brief history. Debate. Empire. Cruel. Prevention.
Laboratory. Deadly. Congress. Welfare. Liberation. Fur. Labor. Promote. Vegetarianism. Ethical.
Front. Day two. K2. Range. Fatality. Savage. Fearsome. Rocky. Steeply. Dramatically.
Attempt. Summit. As of. Dissent. Avalanche. Exhaustion. Despite. Day three. Class and
accent. Accent. Bias. Distinct. Drawl. Stretch. Reassuring. Unintelligent. Mock. Decisive.
Undesirable. Elocution. Respond to. Untrustworthy. Apparently. Accomplished. Prejudice. Irrational. Day
four. He's a hit. Everywhere. Professional. Break records. Tough. Pitch. Field. Mostly. Bat. Naturally.
Muscular. Physically. Imposing. Regular. Outstanding. Draft. Numerous. Day five. The eye in the sky.
Spy. Drone. Remote controlled. Popularity. Explode. Helicopter. Propeller. Extremely. Unique.
Angle. Float. Concern. Military. Destroy. Innocent. Day six. Is it a fair trade? Notice. Label.
Packaging. Sustainable. Poverty. Compassionate. Principle. Current. Invest. Expand. Avoid.
Middleman. Practice. Credit. At any point.